Integration.
Lessons in language learning. A.
Kitty is doing some research on the famous language master Jiao Yuan Ren.
Here is a brief introduction to him.
Read it and answer the questions below.
Jiao Yuan Ren.
A language master.
Jiao Yuan Ren could speak over 30 Chinese dialects and some foreign languages like English, French and German.
He had great talent and strong interest in languages.
He also found useful ways to learn languages.
Jiao thought it was important to spend a lot of time reading, speaking and listening to the language.
Every time he went to a new place, he would talk with the locals.
He quickly learnt their language by putting himself in the language environment.
Also, Jiao always carried a pen and paper with him to write down useful sentences.
Jiao believed that it was better to focus on learning sentences than single words.
In this way he remembered the meanings of the word swell.
It is hard to learn a new language, but if we do it the right way, it will be a lot easier.